I'm joining Jarrod's family for lunch and everything on the menu contains crickets.
Sister-in-law and chef Karen has cooked up her own insect recipes - everything from soup to summer rolls, even cheesecake.
Is it the pepper I'm crunching or is it the cricket I'm crunching?
To me, they sort of, um...
It's earthy.
Mushroomy?
Yeah, mushroomy, yeah.
Yes.
I've got to try cheesecake.
So has that been caramelised, that little cricket?
It's been candied with some granulated honey.
Right.
Those are my favourite.
You know, I don't like this.
You've put coconut in it, haven't you?
Yes.
I cannot stand coconut.
Give me crickets any day to coconut, seriously.
Coconut aside, actually, the food was really good.
I literally thought you were just going to give me, like, a bowl of crickets and say "eat them", but the fact that it's incorporated into diet, you've got it as flour, a little sprinkling and seasoning...